<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--
   Copyright 2016 Google LLC

   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
   you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
   You may obtain a copy of the License at

      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
   limitations under the License.
-->
<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Butterfly Catcher</string>
    <string name="depth_use_explanation" translatable="false">When Depth is enabled on supported devices, virtual objects adapt to the environment by blending in with the real world.</string>
    <string name="button_text_enable_depth" translatable="false">Enable</string>
    <string name="button_text_disable_depth" translatable="false">Disable</string>
    <string name="options_title_with_depth" translatable="false">Your device supports depth</string>
    <string name="options_title_without_depth" translatable="false">Your device does not support depth</string>
    <string name="done" translatable="false">Done</string>

    <string name="options_title_instant_placement" translatable="false">Instant Placement options</string>

    <string name="butterfly1_name">Blue Morpho</string>


    <string name="butterfly2_name">Peacock Butterfly</string>
    <string name="butterfly3_name">Mountain Apollo</string>
    <string name="green_name">Malachite</string>
    <string name="butterfly1_info">As its common name implies, the blue morpho butterfly’s wings are bright blue, edged with black. The blue morpho is among the largest butterflies in the world, with wings spanning from five to eight inches. Their vivid, iridescent blue coloring is a result of the microscopic scales on the backs of their wings, which reflect light. </string>
    <string name="butterfly2_info">The Peacock Butterfly is a species of vibrantly colored butterflies found in two local subspecies, viz. Aglais io caucasica and Aglais io geisha across its range. These are one of the large butterfly species and can be seen best from around February when they come out of hibernation. They get their name from the bright, characteristic eyespots on the wings that often remind of peacock feathers.</string>

    <string name="butterfly3_info">The Apollo is a very large butterfly that is a typical mountain species. They are known for their bright, neat appearance with two pairs of white wings and a white hairy body. This species is particularly interesting to the entomologists and butterfly lovers due to the variety of subspecies. The Apollo butterflies are found around the world in at least 23 different subspecies.</string>
    <string name="green_info">The Malachite Butterfly is a species of tropical butterflies from South America and a member of the brush-footed butterfly group. They are one of the most familiar butterfly species in their distribution range and are known for their unusual coloration and large size. In fact, they are one of the largest butterfly species of the world.</string>
    <string-array name="depth_options_array" translatable="false">
        <item>Enable depth</item>
        <item>Show depth map</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="instant_placement_options_array" translatable="false">
        <item>Enable Instant Placement</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
